Guide to the Records of WNYU RG.39.5
New York University Archives
- Series V: Recorded Programs, 1968-1996; 20 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 3 LP boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 CD box.
  - Cream Commercial for Falstaff Beer, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0559)
  - Cure, Undated (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0328)
  - Deborah M. Newton Chocolate, "Kwanzaa Story", Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0029)
    Adapted by Gabrielle de Banos; Final Mix
  - Deep Throat, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0561)
  - Descendants, Undated (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0301)
  - Dictators (Live, Interview), Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0536)
    Featuring the songs "Young, Fast and Scientific," "Slow Death," and "Next Big Thing"
  - Dislocation Dance song compilation, Undated (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0147)
    Featuring the songs "Don't Knock Me Down" and "Vendetta, Rosemary"
  - Dissonance, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0015)
  - Doctor and the Medics (Interview), Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0228)
  - English Beat, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0285)
  - Ethan of Savage Republic, Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0199)
  - Friendship Show: The Knobby Boys (Final Mix), Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0567)
  - Gingerbread Men "Expectation", Undated (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0172)
    Featuring Mike Mooney (Drums, Vocals), Tim Sprague (Guitar, Vocals), and Carl Thein (Bass). Recorded at Ft. Apache, Boston, MA.
  - Glen Branca, Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0659)
  - Hellhole Aircheck, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0516)
  - Hickey's Remix, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0028)
  - Homer, Magic Bus, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0363)
  - Host Hostess Crazyness, Undated (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0182)
  - HT Jay, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0587)
  - Inspiral Carpets, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0557)
  - Japanese Show - Songs, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0279)
  - Jools Holland, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0366)
  - Keith Rodgers, "Tomorrow", Sleazy Street, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0025)
  - Last Crack: Metallurgy (Interview), Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0026)
  - Liquid Liquid: Grummegroup, Rubbermiro, Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0671)
  - Lisa - Aircheck, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0017)
  - Little Miss Bossy, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0016)
    Original Story by Roger Hargreves
  - "The Little Prince" Final Mix, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0276)
  - LL Cool J, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0007)
  - Love of Rockets, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0578)
  - Lubricated Goat, Tim from Halo of Flies (Interviews), Undated (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0048)
  - Magic School Bus, Maria, Undated (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0055)
  - Marta and Me, Undated (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0179)
  - The Mice, Undated (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0305)
  - Minor Characters (Live), Undated (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0049)
  - The Misfits, Undated (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0311, 39_5_0312)
  - "Mr. Noisy" Final Mix, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0275)
    Original Story by Roger Hargreves, Adapted by Florence Barrau
  - My Summer Vacation Final Mix, Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0232)
    Original Story by Cecilia Johns
  - The Negro and the Political Community, WFUV, Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0392)
    Duration: 00:15:01
    The title of this event recording includes outdated and potentially harmful language. The original language has been maintained to preserve the historical context of the event and promote searchability of the collection.
  - "Pele, Goddess of Fire," Final Mix, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0273)
    Folktale rewritten by Cecilia Johnson, Adapted by Desire Ortiz
  - Penelope Spheeris, Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0222)
  - Peter's Chain Final Mix, Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0250)
  - Pig Bag (Edited), Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0637)
  - Planet of the Lost Things Final Mix, Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0248)
  - Popealopes and Naked Raygun (Interview), Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0381)
    Duration: 00:19:13
  - Promos, Undated (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0089)
  - Pylon, Undated (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0122)
    Featuring the songs "Feast on my Heart," "Danger," and "Volume"
  - Pylon (Interview), Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0497)
    Duration: 00:18:40
  - R.R.V.: Womyn, Undated (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0054)
  - Redd Kross, Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0579)
  - Rhathm Thang Keeps On Rollin', Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0267)
  - Satchmo's Gang, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0262)
  - Splatcats, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0335)
  - Stiff's B-Day Message, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0286)
  - Tape Transfers 4-2015: Mark Dann Recording, Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0374)
  - Terry Terrell, Max Keiser, Goofing Around, Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0658)
    Audio reel 39_5_0658 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Thick and Hairy, Joan Hastings, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0597)
  - Whitney Houston, "Love Will Save the Day" David Morales Remix, Undated (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0046)
  - Wildman Fischer, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0204)
  - Yo La Tengo, Here Now, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0205)
- Series VI: Archived Websites, November 2013-ongoing; 6 websites
  WNYU Radio is the student run radio station found on 89.1 in New York. The website contains a schedule of radio programs and their hosts and descriptions; playlists; charts and top ten lists dating back to 1997; and music requests to listeners. There was a gap in crawling from 2016-2020, when the website redesigned.The program archives of the website date back to March 2005.
  The series also contains websites promoting the radio station or blogging about the radio station. STATIC is WNYU's music magazine and program guide. The magazine has existed in some iteration since the 1980s, but was first launced online in 2023. The website contains concert photos, music reviews, video and text interviews, a list of guests to the radio station, and program guides dating back to 1987. The tumblr contains blog posts promoting different radio programs, playlists, descriptions of episodes, music reviews, and links to articles and interviews from musicians. The blog dates from 2010-2013. The orgsnyc page contains a profile of the radio station.he Facebook page contins promotional posts for the radio programs. Earshot was an alternative news/talk show on WNYU Radio from 2010-2011.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Streaming portions of the websites, such as the audio programs, cannot be captured.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of wnyu.org, staticmag.org, and cargo.site in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored.